kovla.com 2019-04-26

# Privacy Policy - Kovla.com

#### When you visit any website, you automatically provide some of your personal details to the website’s owners. Therefore, each company that operates online has its own privacy policy, having read which the clients can get acquainted with their rights and obligations.

Our website as well has its privacy policy. Read it carefully before you start to use our internet platform in order to experience our services comfortably. Whatever questions you have, do not hesitate to contact us.

If you read our Privacy Policy, you will find out that we use personal information you provide us, when you enter our website or register on it, only for an amelioration of our services. The term “you” as used herein refers to all individuals and/or entities accessing the website for any reason. By continuing to use the website, you are indicating your acceptance to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Private Policy between you and our website. If you do not accept the Private Policy stated here, our website is not willing to allow you to use the website and you should immediately stop using it. You must be at least 18 years of age to use the website. If you are not at least 18 years old, you should immediately stop using the website. It is your responsibility to review this Agreement periodically. We reserves the right to modify this Private Policy from time to time without notice and in its sole discretion at any time by updating this web page, and your continued use of the website after any modifications by us shall constitute your acceptance of such modifications.

Using our website, you can be sure that your personal information will never be transmitted to third parties or used to deceive you or to harm you. If we need to disclose some of your personal information, it will only be made by your prior consent.

Management of your personal information.

##### I. Notice

###### What type of personal information we collect:

When you enter our website, the system automatically captures the Internet provider"s domain name and country that you log from (e.g., "aol.com") as well as the path you follow, when you switch from one page to another (i.e., your "click stream" activity).

###### Visitor Registration or Requests for Information:

We gather that personal details of our clients that they wish to provide to us on a voluntary basis when they register. "Personal information" is that data that helps to identify you as a natural person. It can be, for example, your name or email address; and, in the case of affiliate agreements, your name and company name.

###### Browsing and the use of Cookies:

We use cookie technology for website"s statistical reporting. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a website that is saved on your hard disk by your computer"s browser. It includes information a website may need to customize your specific experience on the website (i.e., rotating images on home page) and to gather statistical data. It can include which pages client visits, what type of content is downloaded, the internet provider"s domain name and country that you come from (e.g. "aol.com," or "umich.edu") and the websites that you visit immediately before and after, coming to our site. But none of this data is associated with you as a particular individual. It is measured only in aggregate. The information in the cookies lets us trace client’s "click stream". Cookies do not capture your individual email address or any type of personal information.  
We also use standard Web server log files that help us to count many visitors and to assess the website"s technical capacity. Such information helps us to organize our pages in the most user-friendly way, and fulfill them with the most appropriate content. We also record information on website traffic, but not on individuals.

You can browse the website without cookies if you configure your browser. You can always reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is set. If you are not familiar with cookies technology, check “Help menu” in your browser to modify your cookie preferences. Each browser has a different policy on cookies.

###### The way we can use the collected information

We may use the data to:

  * Create the most user-friendly website;
  * Fulfill your demand for specific products and services;
  * Customize the services we offer to our clients;
  * Communicate special offers to you, if you agree to get notified about it;
  * Manage your account and your preference list;
  * Ameliorate our website content, structure, products and services;
  * Identify fraudsters;
  * Protect our clients against fraudulent transactions, activities, etc;
  * Provide the answers to your questions and take into account your suggestions.

###### Email, Mailing Lists, and Other Services:

If you send us an email with a question, request, claim, we will shortly reply you, taking into account the content of your letter. We will store your communication in case we will continue it further.

If you agree to, you will receive from us newsletters, account updates, special offers.

###### Linking To Other Websites:

If you leave the website, you have to keep in mind that our Privacy Policy is no longer valid. We recommend you to read the Privacy Policy of another website not to get into trouble. Take into account that if another website contains link to our website, still its Privacy Policy is valid while you experience working on it.

###### Sharing information policy:

Service Providers: We may disclose some of your personal data to third companies that help us to develop new products and services for you. For example, we may work with an outside company to: (a) arrange a database of customers; (b) assist us in distributing emails; (c) assist us with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide us storage and analysis; (d) to prevent fraud. We require that these third companies keep our clients’ information confidentially. In order to ensure the security of our clients, we conclude with them separate agreements that state how they have to process the personal information of our clients.

Other Companies: We may provide some details of your personal data to double-checked outside companies if we suggest that their products or services may be of interest to you.

Business Transitions: We may transfer or share a copy of a personal file in the case, if our internet platform or one of its properties, affiliates or subsidiaries goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company or selling a portion of its assets.

Compliance with Law: We may provide access to information if we are legally obliged to do so, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against unauthorized use of our website, to protect our rights and the rights, property, or safety of our clients.  
We hereby reserve any and all intellectual property rights in the website.

###### Age Restrictions

Those under eighteen years are prohibited to use our website. We work in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Any type of information we may receive from users we believe to be under the age of 18 will be purged from our database.

##### II. Choice

###### Choice/Opt-Out

We may send you from time to time email messages telling about new updates, innovative features and promotional offers. At any point of time you can choose to stop receiving such emails.

You can also read "unsubscribe" sections on our website and follow instructions indicated in it.

##### III. Access

###### Updating Your Information

To modify or delete your personal information, follow the instructions:

  * 1. Log into your account,
  * 2. Select My Account on our Main Page,
  * 3. Scroll down and select My profile,
  * 4. Delete or edit your personal details,
  * 5. Select Save.

Or send a request to our Support team, and we will make the requested changes.

##### IV. Security

###### Security

The security of your personal information is of high importance to us. Therefore, we are committed protecting it. We use firewalls and take security measures to protect our clients against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information.

Our website has VeriSign and McAfee secure certificates that guarantee that it is fully tested, approved and certified by these two leading security systems. When you use it, you can be sure to be protected from any virus, identity theft, credit card fraud, spyware, spam, or online scam on our website.

##### V. Customer Service and Recourse

###### Contacting the Website

Whenever you submit any information to us, when you use any of our services, you consent to policy on a processing of such information.  
If you have any questions, comments or complaints about Privacy Policy and/or the way it affects you, please, contact our Customer support.

###### Acceptance of Privacy Statement

Any type of usage of our website is subject to Privacy Policy, as well Terms and Conditions, if applicable. By using our website, you agree to our Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions.

You warrant that you will not create any databases, websites, software, legal entities and services that will be competitive with our website. If it happens to be, appropriate legal action will be taken. They may include limitation, civil, criminal, and injunctive redress.

We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time without notice and in its sole discretion at any time by updating this web page, and your continued use of the website after any modifications by us shall constitute your acceptance of such modifications.

###### Invalidity

If any provision of this Private Policy is held to be invalid or unenforceable in whole or in part in any jurisdiction, then that provision shall be deemed ineffective in such jurisdiction but shall have no effect on the enforceability of the remaining provisions.

###### Governing law, consent to jurisdiction and limitation on claims

This Private Policy and your use of the website, along with the Information contained therein, shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws

###### Effective Date

This privacy statement was last revised on **registered addresses:**

* * *

ID: 119219 Online

ID: 119651 Online

ID: 114635 Online

ID: 120668 Online

ID: 122506

ID: 119643

ID: 120552

ID: 121089
